<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brighton JUG</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Brighton JUG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2022 Brighton JUG | &lt;a href=&#34;/code-of-conduct/&#34;&gt;Code of Conduct&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 07:09:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting started cloud natively, with Java with Mark Sailes</title>
      <link>/blog/getting-started-cloud-natively/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 07:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/getting-started-cloud-natively/</guid>
      <description>Getting started cloud natively, with Java with Mark Sailes
We are very excited to welcome Mark Sailes. He will be giving a talk on Getting started cloud natively, with Java:
In this talk we will use the AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK) to deploy Java backends for various event driven applications. We&amp;rsquo;ll use the Micronaut framework to create a synchronous REST API, and an asynchronous event worker.
We&amp;rsquo;ll also talk a little about GraalVM native-image and why it&amp;rsquo;s important for AWS Lambda</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Java Agent- modifying Bytecode at runtime for fun and profit with Joseph Beeton</title>
      <link>/blog/the-java-agent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 07:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/the-java-agent/</guid>
      <description>The Java Agent- modifying Bytecode at runtime for fun and profit with Joseph Beeton
We are very excited to welcome Joseph Beeton who will be talking to us about The Java Agent: modifying Bytecode at runtime for fun and profit:
Java Agents are a powerful tool to instrument or modify your application at runtime. But how do they work? In this talk I&amp;rsquo;ll be going through how they work when configured at startup as well as attaching a agent to a running process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thriving in the cloud - Venturing beyond the 12 factors - Grace Jansen and Yasmin Aumeeruddy</title>
      <link>/blog/thriving-in-the-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 07:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/thriving-in-the-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Thriving in the cloud: Venturing beyond the 12 factors
with Grace Jansen and Yasmin Aumeeruddy
————————
Event Format: This is a hybrid event, offering the option to come along in person or join us from anywhere online!
We will be opening the zoom just before 6pm for people to gather and chat.
————————
We are very excited to welcome Grace Jansen and Yasmin Aumeeruddy on their Open Liberty tour. They will be giving a workshop on Thriving in the cloud: Venturing beyond the 12 factors:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Through Tinkering - Tom Cools</title>
      <link>/blog/learning-through-tinkering-tom-cools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 07:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/learning-through-tinkering-tom-cools/</guid>
      <description>Our March Brighton JUG will take place on Tuesday 15th March at 5pm GMT. We will be opening the zoom just before 5pm for people to gather and chat.
Our first speaker will be Tom Cools who will be talking about Learning Through Tinkering
Do you also feel like it’s hard to keep up with all the new tools and frameworks coming your way? You are not alone! By choosing IT, you are choosing to learn for the rest of your life… not an easy task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Development in a Post Log4Shell World - Lee Turner</title>
      <link>/blog/java-development-in-a-post-log4shell-world-lee-turner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 17:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/java-development-in-a-post-log4shell-world-lee-turner/</guid>
      <description>Our second speaker will be Lee Turner - the Lead Backend Developer at Crunch. Lee will be talking to us about Java Development in a Post Log4Shell World
As a Java developer you will probably already be aware of, and are probably in the midst of remediating, the vulnerability that has come to be known as Log4Shell. This is the vulnerability which security researchers disclosed on Friday (10 December 2021) for Apache’s Log4j logging framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing Code is Easy, Being a Great Developer is Hard - Helen Scott</title>
      <link>/blog/writing-code-easy-being-great-developer-is-hard-helen-scott/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 17:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/writing-code-easy-being-great-developer-is-hard-helen-scott/</guid>
      <description>Out first ever Brighton JUG will take place on Tuesday 18th January at 5 pm GMT.
Our first speaker will be Helen Scott who is a Keynote Storyteller at MongoDB. Helen will be talking to us about how Writing Code is Easy, Being a Great Developer is Hard:
tldr; Everything I wish I’d learned about being a developer at University.
We learn to write code at university, bootcamp, or we teach ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Brighton JUG is a group bringing together Java users, enthusiasts and learners. We’re interested in the whole world of Java – android development, server frameworks, interesting tools, applications, development methodologies and so on and so on – anything Java.
Our monthly meetings will include talks, workshops and socials.
Visit our Meetup Page and sign up to come along to our next event or follow us on Twitter for all the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Event Code of Conduct &amp;amp; Anti-Harrassment Policy The Google Developer Groups, Kotlin User Groups and other Community Groups organizing these events [&amp;ldquo;Organizers&amp;rdquo;] are dedicated to providing a harassment-free and inclusive event experience for everyone regardless of gender identity and expression, sexual orientation, disabilities, neurodiversity, physical appearance, body size, ethnicity, nationality, race, age, religion, or other protected category. They do not tolerate harassment of event participants in any form. The Organizers take violations of this policy seriously and will respond appropriately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Brighton</title>
      <link>/silicon-brighton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/silicon-brighton/</guid>
      <description>Brighton JUG is Co-Founded and Supported By Silicon Brighton
Silicon Brighton is a community-led initiative to support digital growth in the region. We work hand-in-hand with the local tech community to provide individuals with free opportunities for networking, training, up-skilling and development; helping people to take their careers and businesses forward.
We offer free events for networking, training, upskilling and development as well as a being an accessible platform for local people and businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
