<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Brighton JUG</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Brighton JUG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2022 Brighton JUG | &lt;a href=&#34;/code-of-conduct/&#34;&gt;Code of Conduct&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 07:09:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Today&#39;s Special - Apache Tika Masala! with Dan Conn</title>
      <link>/blog/apache-tika-dan-conn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 07:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/apache-tika-dan-conn/</guid>
      <description>Meetup link - https://www.meetup.com/brighton-jug/events/290961686/
We are very excited to welcome Dan Conn. He will be giving a talk on Today&amp;rsquo;s Special: Apache Tika Masala!
Apache Tika is an awesome open-source tool which can be used for search indexing, sentiment analysis, detecting the true mime type of a file, or language detection. But Tika can also add some spice to a workflow by helping to highlight threats.
This talk will show Tika’s general use cases and how developers can benefit from its use, but also how it can be used for finding threats in file metadata or content, which may benefit more experienced developers working in security realms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quarkus for Spring Developers with Eric Deandrea</title>
      <link>/blog/quarkus-for-spring-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 07:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/quarkus-for-spring-developers/</guid>
      <description>Quarkus for Spring Developers with Eric Deandrea
We are very excited to welcome Eric Deandrea. He will be giving a talk on Quarkus for Spring Developers:
In this session, I will show concepts and conventions familiar to Spring developers and how those same concepts and conventions can be implemented in Quarkus, all while highlighting similarities and differences between them. Additionally, I will show similarities and differences in how testing is done, highlighting Quarkus Dev Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started cloud natively, with Java with Mark Sailes</title>
      <link>/blog/getting-started-cloud-natively/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 07:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/getting-started-cloud-natively/</guid>
      <description>Getting started cloud natively, with Java with Mark Sailes
We are very excited to welcome Mark Sailes. He will be giving a talk on Getting started cloud natively, with Java:
In this talk we will use the AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK) to deploy Java backends for various event driven applications. We&amp;rsquo;ll use the Micronaut framework to create a synchronous REST API, and an asynchronous event worker.
We&amp;rsquo;ll also talk a little about GraalVM native-image and why it&amp;rsquo;s important for AWS Lambda</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Java Agent- modifying Bytecode at runtime for fun and profit with Joseph Beeton</title>
      <link>/blog/the-java-agent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 07:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/the-java-agent/</guid>
      <description>The Java Agent- modifying Bytecode at runtime for fun and profit with Joseph Beeton
We are very excited to welcome Joseph Beeton who will be talking to us about The Java Agent: modifying Bytecode at runtime for fun and profit:
Java Agents are a powerful tool to instrument or modify your application at runtime. But how do they work? In this talk I&amp;rsquo;ll be going through how they work when configured at startup as well as attaching a agent to a running process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thriving in the cloud - Venturing beyond the 12 factors - Grace Jansen and Yasmin Aumeeruddy</title>
      <link>/blog/thriving-in-the-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 07:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/thriving-in-the-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Thriving in the cloud: Venturing beyond the 12 factors
with Grace Jansen and Yasmin Aumeeruddy
We are very excited to welcome Grace Jansen and Yasmin Aumeeruddy on their Open Liberty tour. They will be giving a workshop on Thriving in the cloud: Venturing beyond the 12 factors:
Enabling applications to really thrive (and not just survive) in cloud environments can be challenging. The original 12 factor app methodology helped to lay out some of the key characteristics needed for cloud-native applications&amp;hellip; but&amp;hellip; as our cloud infrastructure and tooling has progressed, so too have these factors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Through Tinkering - Tom Cools</title>
      <link>/blog/learning-through-tinkering-tom-cools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 07:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/learning-through-tinkering-tom-cools/</guid>
      <description>Our March Brighton JUG will take place on Tuesday 15th March at 5pm GMT. We will be opening the zoom just before 5pm for people to gather and chat.
Our first speaker will be Tom Cools who will be talking about Learning Through Tinkering
Do you also feel like it’s hard to keep up with all the new tools and frameworks coming your way? You are not alone! By choosing IT, you are choosing to learn for the rest of your life… not an easy task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Development in a Post Log4Shell World - Lee Turner</title>
      <link>/blog/java-development-in-a-post-log4shell-world-lee-turner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 17:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/java-development-in-a-post-log4shell-world-lee-turner/</guid>
      <description>Our second speaker will be Lee Turner - the Lead Backend Developer at Crunch. Lee will be talking to us about Java Development in a Post Log4Shell World
As a Java developer you will probably already be aware of, and are probably in the midst of remediating, the vulnerability that has come to be known as Log4Shell. This is the vulnerability which security researchers disclosed on Friday (10 December 2021) for Apache’s Log4j logging framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing Code is Easy, Being a Great Developer is Hard - Helen Scott</title>
      <link>/blog/writing-code-easy-being-great-developer-is-hard-helen-scott/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 17:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/writing-code-easy-being-great-developer-is-hard-helen-scott/</guid>
      <description>Out first ever Brighton JUG will take place on Tuesday 18th January at 5 pm GMT.
Our first speaker will be Helen Scott who is a Keynote Storyteller at MongoDB. Helen will be talking to us about how Writing Code is Easy, Being a Great Developer is Hard:
tldr; Everything I wish I’d learned about being a developer at University.
We learn to write code at university, bootcamp, or we teach ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
