<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloud on Brighton JUG</title>
    <link>/tags/cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cloud on Brighton JUG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2022 Brighton JUG | &lt;a href=&#34;/code-of-conduct/&#34;&gt;Code of Conduct&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 07:09:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quarkus for Spring Developers with Eric Deandrea</title>
      <link>/blog/quarkus-for-spring-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 07:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/quarkus-for-spring-developers/</guid>
      <description>Quarkus for Spring Developers with Eric Deandrea
We are very excited to welcome Eric Deandrea. He will be giving a talk on Quarkus for Spring Developers:
In this session, I will show concepts and conventions familiar to Spring developers and how those same concepts and conventions can be implemented in Quarkus, all while highlighting similarities and differences between them. Additionally, I will show similarities and differences in how testing is done, highlighting Quarkus Dev Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thriving in the cloud - Venturing beyond the 12 factors - Grace Jansen and Yasmin Aumeeruddy</title>
      <link>/blog/thriving-in-the-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 07:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/thriving-in-the-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Thriving in the cloud: Venturing beyond the 12 factors
with Grace Jansen and Yasmin Aumeeruddy
————————
Event Format: This is a hybrid event, offering the option to come along in person or join us from anywhere online!
We will be opening the zoom just before 6pm for people to gather and chat.
————————
We are very excited to welcome Grace Jansen and Yasmin Aumeeruddy on their Open Liberty tour. They will be giving a workshop on Thriving in the cloud: Venturing beyond the 12 factors:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
